https://www.faeriesdance.com/privacy-policy

COME DANCE WITH USGet the latest news, products and discounts by joining our newsletter. Forget the cluttered inbox, too!
Our newsletter is sent only ONCE PER MONTH! GoDon't show this popup again
Skip to Content
Contact Us
Compare ()
Home
MENSShirtsButton DownsPolosPulloversTeesPantsUnderwearKIDSInfants (0-24 mths)Boys & Girls (2T-12)ToysWOMENSTopsTanksTeesTunicsShirts & TopsSweatersBottomsPantsSkirtsShortsOuterwearCoatsJacketsCardigans & WrapsPonchosDressesSwimwearLINGERIEBrasUnderwireWire FreeSports BrasMaternityCamisolesPantiesThongs & BrazilianBikiniHipster & Hi CutBriefsBoy ShortsSleepwearNightgownsPajama SetsLoungewear & SeparatesRobesSOCKSCrew SocksAnkle & Short TopsKnee Highs & TightsKids SocksJEWELRYNecklacesEarringsBracelets & RingsACCESSORIESHats, Gloves & ScarvesPurses & BagsBath & SpaGift BagsBRANDSAaron ChangBe LovebgreenBlue CanoeCielComazo|EarthCottoniqueDo You GreenDream DesignsEarth CreationsEcho VerdeEcoganikEcolutionEcoSkinFrom War to PeaceGoddess GearGreen Tree OrganicHTNaturalsIndigenous DesignsJim Morris T-ShirtsJonänoKelly BLeakey CollectionLes LunesLove NatureMaggie's OrganicsMaha DeviMata TradersNature89OccidenteOf the EarthOrganic ThreadsPACTPants to PovertyPeau-EthiquePerfectly ImperfectPrairie UndergroundPrAnaPueblitoSatori MovementSmart Glass JewelrySolmate SocksSOS From TexasSpun BambooSundrop JewelrySwegmark of SwedenSynergy OrganicTarmaTextureThe Artist JayTree-Free GreetingsVital HemptationsXylemYalaSale
Gift Cards
Account
Home
Privacy and Cookie Policy
Privacy and Cookie Policy
This privacy policy sets out how this website, FaeriesDance.com, uses and protects any information that
you give us while browsing or shopping on our website. Faerie's Dance, Inc. is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected.
Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then
you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Faerie's Dance, Inc. may change
this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page occasionally to ensure
that you agree with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
address information for shipping
For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with better service,
and in particular for the following reasons:
We may contact you by email, phone, or mail if there are any issues with your order including, but not limited to, stock availability, backorders, shipping delays or payment problems.
We may provide certain information to our payment gateway and payment processing companies for the sole purpose of verifying your credit card validity.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
If you opt in to our newsletter, we may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we
think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
Internal record keeping.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or
disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and
secure the information we collect online.
Our website is fully Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS) compliant, verified by CompliAssure™
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive.
Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit
a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application
can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about
your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page
traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for
statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find
useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you,
other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies.
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting
to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links
to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website.
Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst
visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement.
You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
you may unsubscribe from our newsletter at any time using the link at the bottom of any newsletter e-mail or
by letting us know via the Contact Us form.
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes,
you may change your mind at any time by letting us know via the Contact Us form
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to any third parties.
We will not provide or distribute personal information to marketing agencies for the purpose of creating "look alike" lists.
Other than for the express purpose of FaeriesDance.com order payment verification, processing and shipping, no personal information is provided to any third party for any reason.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998.
If you would like a copy of the information held on your account, please email us this
request using our Contact Us form.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete,
please call or email us.
We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies that are collected via the Magento ecommerce shopping software that Faerie's Dance employs, and what information it stores.
Cookie Name
Cookie Description
FORM_KEY
Stores randomly generated key used to prevent forged requests.
PHPSESSID
Your session ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to view and edit their orders.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history, if you have asked for this.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
MAGE-CACHE-SESSID
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE-SECTION-INVALIDATION
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-TIMEOUT
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
SECTION-DATA-IDS
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
PRIVATE_CONTENT_VERSION
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
X-MAGENTO-VARY
Facilitates caching of content on the server to make pages load faster.
MAGE-TRANSLATION-FILE-VERSION
Facilitates translation of content to other languages.
MAGE-TRANSLATION-STORAGE
Facilitates translation of content to other languages.
CancelCancel Continue ShoppingAdd To Cart Please wait... Go To Checkout
COME DANCE WITH US
Get the latest news, products and discounts by joining our newsletter.Forget the cluttered inbox, too! Our newsletter is sent only ONCE PER MONTH!
Sign Up for Our Newsletter: Subscribe
Sitemap  |  Privacy Policy
©Copyright 2020 by Faerie's Dance, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
